Jan Werbrouck | Graphics Programmer

janwerbrouck2000@gmail.com

+44 7544 79 75 32 +32 487 55 10 44

About me

Hi, My name is Jan Werbrouck. I am 23 years old. I grew up in Belgium and started programming when I started my higher education in Game Development. My main interests are graphics programming, coming up with new systems, playing around with shaders and optimisation. I would say I have a lot of curiosity, always open to learning or seeing something new.

Relevant Skills

- · C++
- Unreal Engine (C++ & Blueprints)
- · Modern Graphics APIs: DirectX 12 and a little Vulkan
- · Pix, NSight and RenderDoc
- · Shading languages: **HLSL**, **GLSL** and **UE4** materials.
- · Console Experience: **Xbox One** and **Xbox Series**

Experience

JUNIOR PROGRAMMER | SEPTEMBER 2021 - CURRENT | CLIMAX STUDIOS

Worked as a part of the graphics team of the PC port of the PS5 exclusive Returnal for Sony in Unreal Engine. This included adding new material nodes, fixing shader issues, profiling and optimising rendering and memory and loading speed issues.

Currently working on the optimisation team for another AAA Title for Microsoft, profiling and optimising the game for Xbox.

Internship | Februari 2021 - June 2021 | Climax Studios

Programming in Unreal Engine C++ and implementing multiplayer functionality for an early prototype in Unreal Engine. Also started working on the PC Port of the PS5 game Returnal.

STUDENT JOB | I-SOLV-IT

(joris@isolvit.be | +32 484 95 86 46)

Working on Windows applications, using **SQL**, **C**# and **WPF**.

Education

DIGITAL ARTS AND ENTERTAINMENT | 2018 - 2021 | HOWEST - KORTRIJK

· Professional Bachelor in Game Development

Languages

- Dutch Native
- **English** Fluent (C2)